question_data = [
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The Lego Group was founded in 1932.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Jingle Bells was originally meant for Thanksgiving","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Slovakia is a member of European Union-","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"King Gizzard &amp; The Lizard Wizard&#039;s album &quot;Nonagon Infinity&quot; can be looped seamlessly.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
]
